Guide to the 7th Regiment Records 1767-1983 (bulk, 1830-1947) MS 556
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV: Francis D. Landon, 1908-1918
  - Subseries 2: Military Education, 1912-1917
    - Army Service Schools - Printed Examination Booklets, 1917, undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 11)
    - [Army Service Schools] - Proposed Solution to Griepenkerl Problem, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 12)
    - [Army Service Schools] - Residence List of Officers at Fort Leavenworth, 1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 13)
    - [Army Service Schools] - Invitation, [1914] (Offsite-box 26, Folder 14)
    - School of the Line and Staff - Map Problems, 1914-1916 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 15)
    - Board of Instruction - 7th Reg't - Instructions to First Year Class, 1915 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 16)
    - [Map Problems] - Suggestions for the Preparation of Maneuver Problems, 1913 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 17)
    - [Map Problems] - [Problems Composed by Landon], 1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 18)
    - Notes on Map Drawing/Map Reading, [1915] (Offsite-box 26, Folder 19)
    - [Lecture Notes] - Fort Leavenworth, 1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 20)
    - Notes on Civil War Battles, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 21)
    - Typewritten Notes on Military Tactics, 1915, 1916, undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 22)
    - Synopses of Books, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 23)
    - Sample Quiz Questions and Answers, [1914] (Offsite-box 26, Folder 24)
    - Quizzes, 1914-1916 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 25)
    - Examination - American Campaigns, [1914] (Offsite-box 26, Folder 26)
    - NY Service Schools - Map Problem #3, 1915-1916 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 1)
    - NY School of the Line and Staff - Bulletins, 1914-1915 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 2)
    - NY School of the Line and Staff - Infantry Officers' Examinations, 1915-1916 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 3)
    - NY School of the Line Map Problem #6, 1915-1916 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 4)
    - NY School of the Line - Organizational Table of a U.S. Infantry Division, 1915-1916 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 5)
    - NY National Guard - Typescript of Pamphlet re Trench Warfare, 1916 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 6)
    - Advertisement for Book - Battle Fire Training, Undated (Offsite-box 27, Folder 7)
    - Typescript - Manual for Infantrymen, Undated (Offsite-box 27, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Camp Merritt, 1918-1919
    The Camp Merritt, NJ subseries contains, for the most part, material created by or relating to the Morale Office at that facility. A small portion of the material in the subseries concerns the Camp in general, and is not specific to the Morale Office. Included is correspondence to and from the Morale Office. Note that this folder group is distinct from the General Correspondence subseries, and includes material addressed to other offices on Camp Merritt, but routed to and answered by the Morale Office. Letters received by the Morale Office are arranged chronologically in a folder titled Morale Office - Letters Received. Retained copies of the Morale Office's replies are arranged in folders by the name of the letter's recipient. Subjects include: programs to maintain the morale of soldiers stationed at Camp Merritt (e.g. sporting events, Christmas decorations, 4th of July fireworks, etc.); commemorative medals for the schoolchildren of Bergen County, NJ, to be paid for by the personnel of the Camp; and weekly reports to the war Department on the state of the soldiers' morale.
    - Morale Office - Letters Received, 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 9)
    - Morale Office - Letters Received - Letters from Children, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 10)
    - Morale Office - Circular Letters Received, 1918, undated (Offsite-box 27, Folder 11)
    - Morale Office - Major [ ] Axton -, 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 12)
    - Morale Office - Bank of Coney Island, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 13)
    - Morale Office - Chaplain [ ] Beebe, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 14)
    - Morale Office - Dept. of Labor, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 15)
    - Morale Office - Dreges & Clost, 1918 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 16)
    - Morale Office - Wm. H. Edwards, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 17)
    - Morale Office - [ ] Evans, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 18)
    - Morale Office - John Gorman, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 19)
    - Morale Office - Matthew P. Halpin, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 20)
    - Morale Office - Curtis Harrington, 1918 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 21)
    - Morale Office - Ensign Ernest R. Holz, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 22)
    - Morale Office - Grace W. Hurd, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 23)
    - Morale Office - Iron Steamboat Co., 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 24)
    - Morale Office - Edwin Newall Lewis, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 25)
    - Morale Office - Mandalay Line, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 26)
    - Morale Office - Arthur McAleenan, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 27)
    - Morale Office - Col. E. L. Munson, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 28)
    - Morale Office - Thomas H. Neary, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 29)
    - Morale Office - Col. Charles M. O'Connor, Undated (Offsite-box 27, Folder 30)
    - Morale Office - Pain's Fireworks Co., 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 31)
    - Morale Office - Capt. F. Peterson, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 32)
    - Morale Office - Marian R. Ramsey, 1918 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 33)
    - Morale Office - Joseph Raycroft, 1918 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 34)
    - Morale Office - Alphonso Scerbo, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 35)
    - Morale Office - Shamrock Towing Co., 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 36)
    - Morale Office - Mrs. E. M. Speer, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 37)
    - Morale Office - Maj. [ ] Sullivan, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 38)
    - Morale Office - Mrs. E. M. Townsend, 1918 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 39)
    - Morale Office - Winton J. White, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 40)
    - Morale Office - Whitehead & Hoag Co., 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 41)
    - Morale Office - B. C. Wooster, 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 42)
    - Morale Office - Wynkoop Hallenbeck Crawford Co., 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 43)
    - Morale Office - Memoranda Received, 1918 Dec.-1919 Mar. (Offsite-box 27, Folder 44)
    - Morale Office - Memoranda from War Dept. Morale Branch, 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 45)
    - Morale Office - Memoranda Sent, 1918 Nov.-1919 Aug., undated (Offsite-box 27, Folder 46)
    - Morale Office - [Internal Memorandum], 1919 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 47)
    - Morale Office - Orders and Circulars, 1918 Oct.-Nov. (Offsite-box 27, Folder 48)
    - Morale Office - Weekly Morale Reports, 1918 Nov.-1919 Sept. (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
    - Morale Office - War Dept. General Orders, 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 2)
    - Morale Office - Minutes of Morale Committee, 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
    - Morale Office - [Proposed Designs for Children's Medal], [1918] (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
    - Morale Office - Lists of Schools in Bergen County, NJ, [1919] (Offsite-box 28, Folder 5)
    - Morale Office - Case of Pvt. Wm. Franklin, 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 6)
    - Morale Office - Distribution of Posters, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 7)
    - Morale Office - Schedule of Service Calls, 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 8)
    - Morale Office - Bills & Receipts re Children's Medals, 1918-1919, undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 9)
    - Morale Office - [Returns of Personnel], 1919 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 10)
    - Morale Office - Distribution of Red Cross Packages & Xmas Trees, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 11)
    - Morale Office - Organizational Chart of Morale Agencies, 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 12)
    - Morale Office - Booklet - Merritt Hall - Soldiers' Club, [1918] (Offsite-box 28, Folder 13)
    - [Notes for Booklet], [1918] (Offsite-box 28, Folder 14)
    - Booklet - Naturalization Laws and Regulations, 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 15)
    - Booklet - War Risk Insurance Act, 1919 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 16)
    - Petition of David Richard Gottlieb for Naturalization, 1919 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 17)
    - List of Recreation and Entertainment Buildings at Camp Merritt, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 18)
    - YMCA school Enrollment, [1919] (Offsite-box 28, Folder 19)
    - Telephone Directories, 1919 Aug., undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 20)
    - [Return of Garrison], 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 21)
    - Sketch of [Shoulder Patch], Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 22)
    - Clipping, 1919 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 23)
  - Single Folder Subseries, 1909-1918
    - HQ, port of Embarkation, Hoboken NJ - Special Order, 1919 Nov. 4 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 24)
    - War Department - General Orders, 1913, 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 25)
    - New York National Guard - General Orders, 1914, 1915 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 26)
    - 7th Regiment HQ - General Orders, 1909 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 27)
    - Tables of Organization and Equipment, U.S. Army, 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 28)
    - Notebook, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 29)
    - Doggerel, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 30)
    - Clippings, 1914, 1918 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 31)
    - Advertisement for Rifle Scope, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 32)
    - Clippings of Maps from WWI era, 1914, 1915, 1916 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 33)
    - Blank Contour Sheets for map Drawing, Undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 34)
  - Maps
    Most of these are of the Pennsylvania - Maryland border, and were evidently used in conjunction with Map Problems. Other maps depict the Eastern and Western Fronts in the First World War, Fort Leavenworth and its environs, and locations in Central Europe.
    - Maps--Europe, Ft. Leavenworth and vicinity, Mexico, locations in U.S. (other than Pa-MD border), oversize contour sheets (Box 86 (oversize))
    - Maps--Oversize and PA-MD Border (Box 87 (oversize))
  - Pamphlets, 1908-1918
    - Barry, Lt. Walter M. Dreams, Joys & Sorrows of the 13th Infantry, [1918] (Offsite-box 29)
    - Bedier, Joseph. How Germany Seeks to Justify Her Atrocities, 1915 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Bjornstad, Capt. A.W. The German Army, 1916 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Burnham, Lt. Col. W. P. Army Service Schools - Annual Report, 1913 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Conger, Capt. [ ]. Preparing Tactical Problems, 1916 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Eames, Capt. E. H. Military Maps Explained, 1908 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Eltinge, Capt. Le Roy. Psychology of War, 1915 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Eltinge, Maj. Le Roy. Notes on Cavalry, 1917 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Eltinge, Maj. Le Roy. Field Fortifications and Demolitions, 1917 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Fiske, Capt. H. B. Some Notes on the Solution of Tactical Problems, 1916 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Fiske, Maj. H. B. Notes on Infantry, 1917 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Ford, Clyde Sinclair. The Balkan Wars, 1915 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Hayne, Capt. P. T. Lectures on Cavalry, 1915 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Hitt, Capt. Parker. Manual for the Solution of Military Ciphers, 1916 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Holbrook, Col. W. A. Notes Preliminary Conference on Conduct of War, 1916 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Hutchinson, Maj. James. Notes on Military Map Reading, 1915 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Jarvis, N. S., M. D. The Medical Side of the Army Maneuvers in Texas, 1911 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Mauborgne, Lt. J. O. An Advanced Problem in Cryptography and its Solution, 1914 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Moore, Maj. G. D. The Casey Firing Problem, [1913] (Offsite-box 29)
    - Morrison, Maj. John F. Lectures on Patrols, Advance Guards, and Outposts (2 copies), 1909 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Morrison, Maj. J. F. Applied Minor Tactics (2 copies), 1911 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Naylor, Capt. W. K. The Principles of Strategy as Illustrated by the Civil War, 1916 (Offsite-box 30)
    - Porter, Col. J. B. Suggested Forms for Military Passes, etc. as well as for Certain Military Agreements, such as Armistices, etc. (2 copies), 1914 (Offsite-box 30)
    - Porter, Col. John Biddle. The Geneva and Hague Conventions, 1914 (Offsite-box 30)
    - Sherill, Capt. C. O. Military Map Reading, 1909 (Offsite-box 30)
    - Spaulding, Capt. George R. Notes on Bridges and Bridging, 1916 (Offsite-box 30)
    - Wadhams, Maj. Sanford H. Elements of Military Hygiene, 1914 (Offsite-box 30)
    - Warfield, Capt. A. B. Notes on Field Artillery, 1917 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [NY] Adjutant General. Practical talk on Summer Maneuvers, 1912 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] Divisional Outposts, 1916 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] European Frontiers, Undated (Offsite-box 30)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America. War Camp Community Service: The Second Six Months, [1918] (Offsite-box 30)
    - [U. S. War Department.] Facts of Interest Concerning the Military Resources of the United States, 1914 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] Ready Reference Notes for the Line Class in the Solution of Division and Brigade Problems Involving the Use of Signal Corps Units (2 copies), Undated (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] Instruction in Equitation, 1917 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] A Synopsis of "The Rifle in War", 1914 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [U. S. War Department.] Manual of the Bayonet, 1913 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] Sample Map Maneuvers, 1915 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] Notes on Field Fortification, 1914 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] Regulations, 1913 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] A Study in Staff Supply, [1915] (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Army Service Schools.] Notes on Field Fortification, 1912 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [Gov't Printing Office.] Secretary of War Garrison's Explanation of the Military Policy Recommended by Him and Approved by the President, [1915] (Offsite-box 30)
    - [U. S. Army.] Questions in Guard Manual for Privates for Orderlies and Color Sentinels, 1915 (Offsite-box 30)
    - [U. S. Army Signal Corps.] Field Message Book (blank), Undated (Offsite-box 30)
    - [7th Regiment.] Bulletin for the use of Officers and Enlisted Men During the Connecticut Maneuver Campaign, 1912 (Offsite-box 30)
    - U. S. War Department. Army Song Book, 1918 (Offsite-box 30)
- Series V: Robert M. Lester, 1942-1951
  This series contains the World War II era files of Lt. Robert M. Lester, who served in the New York State Guard, Headquarters and Service Company. Topics include 7th Regiment history, training, the Second Service Command Tactical School, and Camp Smith. The bulk of the material is memoranda and administrative items. Lester's collection of photographs can be found in Series XIV: Visual Materials.
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1942-1951 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 1)
  - Certificates, 1943-1945 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 2)
  - "Outline of Talk to Officer Candidates", 1944 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 3)
  - New York Guard Association, Delegates to Convention, 1945 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 4)
- Series VI: Armory, 1860-1888
  This series consists of materials relating to the building and maintenance of the 7th Regiment armories. Most of the material relates to the armory on Park Avenue and 66th Street, built in 1880. For other information see the reports of the Armory Committee under Committees, Series I: Headquarters.
  - Regulations of the National Guard Armory, 1860 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of Armory, 1861, 1886 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 2)
  - Seventh Regiment New Armory Fund, 1876-1880 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Acts and Laws re: New Armory, 1879, undated (Offsite-box 32, Folder 4)
  - List of "Work Done by the Regiment" on the Armory, 1893 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 5)
  - Account Book--Cash Book--New Armory Fund, 1876-1880 (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 302)
  - Account Book--Subscription Book--Armory Fund, [1877] (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 303)
  - Visitors Book, 1860-1874 (Offsite-box SR-50, Volume 304)
  - Visitors Book, 1881-1883 (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 305)
  - Guestbook, 1883-1888 (Offsite-box SR-50, Volume 306)
- Series VII: Histories, 1831-1956
  This series contains various histories of the 7th Regiment, some of which are general regimental histories (primarily commemorative or promotional), and others histories or reminiscences of specific time periods, events, or designations of the regiment. The account of the Astor Place Riot is told from a man claiming to be both an instigator of the conflict and a member of 7th Regiment sent to suppress the riot.
  - 7th Regiment, 1908-1956, undated (Offsite-box 32, Folder 6)
  - 207th A.A.A. Group, 1945 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 7)
  - 7th A.A.A. Battalion (A.W.) (2 copies), 1945 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 8)
  - 771st A.A.A. Gun Battalion, Notes (3 copies), 1951 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 9)
  - 7th Regiment- Specific Events/Items, 1953, 1961, undated (Offsite-box 32, Folder 10)
  - "Private Journal"/"Prison Diary" - Charleston Prison, Alexander Shaler, 1864 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 11)
  - "American 'National Guards,' A Brief Memoir... by Henry O'Reilly", 1877 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 12)
  - "Memoir of Camp Clinton", 1831 (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 307)
  - Camp Scott Diary, 1861 (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 308)
  - Account of 1849 Astor Place Riot (typescript), [1889] (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 309)
  - "A Brief History of the Seventh Regiment", 1931 (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 310)
  - "History of the Seventh Regiment, 1889-1918" by DeWitt Clinton Falls (in 2 parts; 2 copies), 1932 (Offsite-box SR-49, Volume 311)
  - Recollections of Wm. H Owen, written by Wm. H Owen Jr., 1938 (Offsite-box SR-49, Volume 312)
  - "Reminiscence of the Flour Riot in 1837" (2 copies), Undated (Offsite-box SR-49, Volume 313)
  - "March of the 7th Regiment N.G.N.Y. to Washington" (typescript of 1861 sermon), Undated (Offsite-box SR-49, Volume 314)
- Series VIII: Scrapbooks, 1852-1946
  The scrapbooks in this collection contain various types of material including clippings, ephemera, photographs, correspondence, and cartoons. Some scrapbooks pertain to the regiment as a whole, other are scrapbooks of specific individuals, and some cover particular events or topics such as the regiment's centennial celebration, and the Croton Dam strike. Two scrapbooks from 1909 and 1912 document the 7th Regiment's participation in war games. The scrapbooks are arranged chronologically.
  - "Crystal Palace Album & Hippodrome Gazette", 1852-1857 (Offsite-box SR-49, Volume 315)
  - Maj. Kenneth C. Miller, 1855-1865 (Offsite-box SR-51, Volume 316)
  - DeWitt Clinton Falls, 1856-1892 (Offsite-box SR-51, Volume 317)
  - Scrapbook, 1857-1860 (Offsite-box SR-51, Volume 318)
  - Scrapbook, 1860-1862 (Offsite-box SR-51, Volume 319)
  - Scrapbook, 1868-1872 (Offsite-box SR-51, Volume 320)
  - Scrapbook (with orders), 1869 (Offsite-box SR-52, Volume 321)
  - Scrapbook, 1869-1872 (Offsite-box SR-52, Volume 322)
  - Scrapbook, 1872 (Offsite-box SR-52, Volume 323)
  - Scrapbook, 1872-1878 (Offsite-box SR-52, Volume 324)
  - Scrapbook, 1873-1878 (Offsite-box SR-52, Volume 325)
  - Scrapbook, 1875-1876 (Offsite-box SR-53, Volume 326)
  - Scrapbook, 1879-1886 (Offsite-box SR-53, Volume 327)
  - Scrapbook, 1883-1887 (Offsite-box SR-54, Volume 328)
  - Scrapbook, 1885-1890 (Offsite-box SR-53, Volume 329)
  - Scrapbook, 1886-1889 (Offsite-box SR-54, Volume 330)
  - Scrapbook, 1889 (Offsite-box SR-57, Volume 331)
  - Scrapbook, 1889 (Offsite-box SR-53, Volume 332)
  - [DeWitt Clinton Falls], [1891-1897] (Offsite-box SR-54, Volume 333)
  - [DeWitt Clinton Falls], 1891-1895 (Offsite-box SR-54, Volume 334)
  - Scrapbook, 1893-1896 (Offsite-box SR-55, Volume 335)
  - DeWitt Clinton Falls, 1898-1901 (Offsite-box SR-55, Volume 336)
  - Spanish American War, 1898 (Offsite-box SR-55, Volume 337)
  - Francis F. Spies, 1898-1899 (Offsite-box SR-55, Volume 338)
  - Silas B. Brower, 1899-1900 (Offsite-box SR-55, Volume 339)
  - Croton Dam Strike, 1900 (Offsite-box SR-56, Volume 340)
  - Croton Dam Strike, 1900 (Offsite-box SR-56, Volume 341)
  - DeWitt Clinton Falls, 1902-1905 (Offsite-box SR-56, Volume 342)
  - DeWitt Clinton Falls, 1906-1908 (Offsite-box SR-56, Volume 343)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1906 (Offsite-box SR-58, Volume 344)
  - DeWitt Clinton Falls, 1908-1911 (Offsite-box SR-59, Volume 345)
  - Maneuvers, 1909 (Offsite-box SR-57, Volume 346)
  - DeWitt Clinton Falls, 1912-1916 (Offsite-box SR-59, Volume 347)
  - Maneuvers, Connecticut, 1912 (Offsite-box SR-60, Volume 348)
  - Union League Club, 1913 (Offsite-box SR-59, Volume 349)
  - Mexican Border/ World War I, 1916 (Offsite-box SR-57, Volume 350)
  - Warren G. Harding, [1923] (Offsite-box SR-60, Volume 351)
  - "The National Guard Alphabet"-- Cartoons, 1924-1929 (Offsite-box SR-61, Volume 352)
  - DeWitt Clinton Falls, 1926-1932 (Offsite-box SR-61, Volume 353)
  - [DeWitt Clinton Falls], compiler-- Cartoon Book, 1931-1934 (Offsite-box SR-61, Volume 354)
  - Scrapbook, 1932-1933 (Offsite-box SR-60, Volume 355)
  - DeWitt Clinton Falls, 1932-1937 (Offsite-box SR-62, Volume 356)
  - "Kipling's Autobiography"-- Clippings, 1937 (Offsite-box SR-61, Volume 357)
  - Scrapbook, 1937 (Offsite-box SR-61, Volume 358)
  - Clippings, 1943-1946 (Offsite-box SR-61, Volume 359)
- Series IX: Ephemera, 1820-1976
  This series includes primarily items related to 7th Regiment events, World War I, the 7th's Mexican border service, companies, and veterans. Material related to 7th Regiment events includes programs, tickets, announcements, and menus for various dinners, balls, excursions, celebrations, and concerts (1820-1964). World War I material contains instructional, promotional, and recruitment items from the Red Cross and other relief organizations, the armed services, the U.S. Food Administration, and various other sources. Ephemera related to the 7th's Mexican border service in 1916 is primarily newspaper clippings, also some New York State election material. Company ephemera mostly documents company events, such as dinners, parties, and entertainment. Veteran material is also mainly events related, especially annual dinners and reunions.
  Other material in this series includes 7th Regiment and National Guard recruitment items; pamphlets, brochures, flyers, posters, and circulars from various sources; Civil War broadsides that advertise amusements; training material; divine service and memorial programs; various ads and catalogs; election nominee slips and calling cards; postcards; non-military or 7th Regiment certificates; and newspaper clippings.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Digital copies of selected ephemera are available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
  - Events, 1820-1879 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1)
  - Events, 1880-1887 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 2)
  - Events, 1888-1906 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 3)
  - Events--Centennial Celebration, 1906 May 6 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 4)
  - Events, 1908 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 5)
  - Events--Celebration of the 50th Anniversary of Departure for Washington, April 19, 1861, 1911 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 6)
  - Events, 1912-1916 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 7)
  - Events, 1918-1921 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 8)
  - Events, 1922-1937 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 9)
  - Events--Farewell Dinner, 207th Coast Artillery, 1940 Dec. 16 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1)
  - Events, 1940-1947 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 2)
  - Events--Military Ball, 1948 Dec. 11 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 3)
  - Events, 1948-1964, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 4)
  - World War I--Circulars, Pamphlets, Flyers, 1916-1922, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 5)
  - World War I--Booklets, 1916-1918, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 6)
  - World War I--Booklets, 1918-1919, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
  - World War I--Memorials, 1919, 1927, undated (Offsite-box 34, Folder 8)
  - Mexican Border Service--Election Material, 1916, [1916] (Offsite-box 35, Folder 1)
  - Mexican Border Service--Clippings, 1916, [1916] (Offsite-box 35, Folder 2)
  - Mexican Border Service--Clippings, 1916, [1916] (Offsite-box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mexican Border Service--Clippings, 1916, [1916] (Offsite-box 35, Folder 4)